<!--
    * Copyright (C) [2023 - Present] - Xero
    *
    * Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
    * you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
    * You may obtain a copy of the License at
    *
    *     https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
    *
    * Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
    * distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
    * WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
    * See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
    * limitations under the License.
    -->
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Coffee Drop</string>
    <string name="dollar_sign">\$</string>
    <string name="price">%.2f</string>
    <string name="reviews">(%s reviews)</string>

    <string name="description_menu">Menu Icon</string>
    <string name="description_avatar">Avatar</string>
    <string name="description_search">Search Icon</string>
    <string name="description_clear">Clear Icon</string>
    <string name="description_rating">Rating</string>
    <string name="description_add_button">Add Button</string>
    <string name="description_for_you_image">For You Image</string>
    <string name="description_no_matches">No Matches</string>
    <string name="description_coffee_image">Coffee Image</string>
    <string name="description_back_btn">Back</string>
    <string name="description_heart_btn">Favorite</string>

    <string name="headline_1">Find the best</string>
    <string name="headline_2">coffee for you</string>
    <string name="search_bar_placeholder">Find your coffee…</string>
    <string name="special_for_you">Special For You</string>
    <string name="five_coffee_beans_to_try">Five Coffee Beans You Have to Try</string>
    <string name="special_for_you_headline">The best that\'ll make you rediscover caffeine wonder</string>
    <string name="no_matching_results">No Coffee Matching this Filter</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="read_more">read more</string>
    <string name="read_less">read less</string>

    <string name="cappuccino">Cappuccino</string>
    <string name="mocha">Mocha</string>
    <string name="espresso">Espresso</string>
    <string name="double_espresso">Double Espresso</string>
    <string name="cortado">Cortado</string>
    <string name="latte">Latte</string>

    <string name="cappuccino_description">
        Cappuccino is a popular coffee beverage that originated in Italy. It consists of equal
        parts of espresso, steamed milk, and milk foam.\n\nThe drink is typically served in a small cup,
        and the espresso is first brewed and poured
        into the cup. Then, the steamed milk is added, followed by a layer of milk foam on top.
        The foam is often decorated with a sprinkle of cocoa powder or cinnamon.\n\nCappuccinos are known
        for their rich, creamy texture and bold coffee flavor.
        They are often enjoyed as a breakfast or mid-morning drink, but can be enjoyed anytime throughout
        the day.\n\nCappuccinos can be made with a variety of milk types, such as whole, skim, or soy milk,
        and can also be flavored with syrups or spices for added sweetness or flavor.
    </string>

    <string name="mocha_description">
        Mocha, also known as a mochaccino, is a type of coffee beverage that combines espresso with chocolate.\n\nTo
        make a mocha, a shot of espresso is brewed and mixed with chocolate syrup or melted chocolate. Steamed
        milk is then added, along with a layer of milk foam on top. The drink is often finished with a sprinkle of
        cocoa powder or shaved chocolate on top.\n\nMochas can be made with various types of chocolate, such as dark, milk,
        or white chocolate, depending on
        personal preference. They can also be served hot or iced, and with a variety of milk types, such as whole,
        skim, or soy milk.\n\nMochas are known for their rich, chocolatey flavor, and are a popular coffee drink among
        those with a sweet tooth. They are often enjoyed as a dessert or as an indulgent treat during a coffee break.
    </string>

    <string name="espresso_description">
        Espresso is a strong, concentrated coffee beverage that is made by forcing hot water through finely ground coffee beans
        under high pressure.\n\nTo make espresso, a small amount of finely ground coffee beans is packed into a metal filter
        basket called a portafilter. The portafilter is then attached to an espresso machine, which uses high pressure to force hot water
        through the coffee grounds and extract a small, concentrated shot of coffee.\n\nEspresso is typically served in small, demitasse-sized
        cups and has a thick, creamy layer of foam on top called crema. The crema is formed during the brewing process and is a result of the
        high pressure used to extract the coffee. Espresso can be enjoyed on its own, as a shot, or can be used as a base for a variety of coffee
        beverages, such as cappuccinos, lattes, and macchiatos. It is known for its strong, bold flavor and is a popular choice among coffee lovers
        who enjoy a more intense coffee experience.
    </string>

    <string name="double_espresso_description">
        A double espresso, also known as a doppio, is a coffee beverage made by extracting a double shot of espresso instead of a single shot.\n\nTo
        make a double espresso, twice the amount of coffee grounds are used and packed into the portafilter, and twice the amount of hot water
        is forced through the grounds to extract a larger, more concentrated shot of coffee.\n\nLike a regular espresso, a double espresso is typically
        served in a small, demitasse-sized cup and has a thick layer of crema on top. However, due to the larger amount of coffee used, a double espresso
        has a stronger, bolder flavor and a more intense caffeine content than a single shot of espresso.\n\nDouble espressos are often enjoyed by those
        who prefer a stronger coffee taste or who need an extra jolt of caffeine to start their day. They can be consumed on their own or used as a base
        for other coffee beverages such as lattes, cappuccinos, and macchiatos.
    </string>

    <string name="cortado_description">
        Cortado is a coffee beverage that originated in Spain and is becoming increasingly popular in other parts of the world. It is made by combining equal
        parts of espresso and steamed milk.\n\nTo make a cortado, a shot of espresso is brewed and poured into a small glass or ceramic cup. Then, steamed milk
        is added to the espresso, creating a creamy and smooth texture. The ratio of espresso to milk is typically equal, although this can vary based on personal
        preference.\n\nCortados are known for their balance of strong coffee flavor and rich, velvety texture from the steamed milk. They are often served in smaller
        portions than a latte or cappuccino, making them a perfect option for those who prefer a smaller, less milky coffee beverage.\n\nThe word "cortado" comes from
        the Spanish word "cortar," which means "to cut." This refers to the way the espresso shot is "cut" with the steamed milk to create the perfect balance of coffee
        and milk flavor. Cortados are typically served as a morning or mid-day coffee beverage and are enjoyed by those who
        appreciate a rich and flavorful coffee without too much milk.
    </string>

    <string name="latte_description">
        A latte is a popular coffee beverage that is made with espresso and steamed milk. It is typically served in a tall glass or ceramic cup and is known for
        its smooth and creamy texture.\n\nTo make a latte, a shot of espresso is brewed and poured into the bottom of the cup. Then, steamed milk is added, creating
        a layer of creamy foam on top.The ratio of milk to espresso can vary, but typically there is more milk than espresso in a latte.\n\nLattes can be customized
        with various flavors, such as vanilla, caramel, or hazelnut, by adding flavored syrups or sauces to the espresso and milk mixture. They can also be topped
        with whipped cream, cocoa powder, or cinnamon for added flavor and decoration.\n\nLattes are often enjoyed as a morning or mid-day coffee beverage and are a
        popular choice among those who prefer a milder coffee taste. They are also a popular option for those who enjoy a milky coffee beverage with a touch of sweetness.
    </string>
</resources>